Chime
First off, what the heck are you blubbering about over there?
It's contagious.
Well, stop it!
I... I washed it, so don't worry. It's not dirty. And it won't curse you.
That's not the issue. I know that.
Don't cry, it's annoying!
Tell me what happened between you and Kaze Haya.
I... I realized how much I liked him.
Are you dating?
Did you tell him that you liked him? Did he tell you?
Huh?
Did I?
Or did he?
Of course not!
Really? You two aren't going out?
No way that happened!
You don't know that!
Like, what if he gets caught up in the moment?
He could totally ask you out!
Wha... wait a minute...
Are you telling me there's a chance that Kaze Haya might like me back?
Until a little while ago, I was a total loner who didn't even have a single person to talk to.
It doesn't matter. Kaze Haya wouldn't judge someone for that.
He's kind. And he looks after people.
And he... sees you for who you really are.
Yeah. And when he smiles, no matter what, you can't help but smile with him.
Exactly! But also, if you mess up with something important, he'll hold you accountable!
Mm-hmm.
He's surprisingly short-tempered, and he just hates when people do the wrong thing!
Regardless of gender, everyone looks up to him!
He's honest... and cheerful... cute!
Why the heck am I sharing all this with you?!
I love this. I've never talked like this... with anyone before.
Despite the things Kurumi says, I can tell that she acknowledges me for who I truly am.
In that way, she's just like Kaze Haya.
Why'd this happen? It should've been perfect timing!
We started high school, and I even got everyone to support the idea of us being together!
Now was the time... to make him fall for me!
The perfect time!
But in the end, it was all for nothing!
Earlier, I... accidentally made Kaze Haya think that I like Pin Arai!
Huh?!
No matter what I say now, he'll probably assume I'm just denying it out of embarrassment!
How did that happen?!
I miscalculated, okay?!
I don't care anymore.
Kaze Haya was never interested in me.
Not in that way.
I already knew that.
Does it really matter if he finds out what I did, or thinks I like someone else?
Yes, it does.
I mean... I didn't want him to think I like Sanada.
It felt awful being misunderstood.
I understand.
So I'm sure he will too if you just talk to him.
You think that he'll understand everything as long as I just talk to him?
Are you stupid?
But still, I can tell, I don't think she would ever be happy leaving things like this.
I know I wouldn't be, and we share the same feelings for the same person.
We both love Kaze Haya.
But sharing the same feelings makes it difficult.
Is it really not possible for us to be friends?
And if we're not friends, then I wonder what that would make us.
Is there a word for it?
Are we nothing but strangers again?
Or maybe... something completely new and different?
Uh... Oh, there you are!
Huh?
Is your stomach okay?
Yeah, it's better now.
We got worried when you disappeared on us like that.
I'll be able to play in the games tomorrow, though.
Well, that's good at least.
Yeah!
See you tomorrow, then.
Okay?
Bye-bye!
Bye!
It's pretty late now.
Wanna hang somewhere?
In other words, you're hungry?
Karumi!
Let's be on the same team!
It'll be great!
Oh, hey!
What?!
No way!
You seriously don't have a crush on anyone?!
You're so cute!
What a waste!
I'm so glad we became such good friends!
Same here!
Right?
Being in the same circle is the best!
Huh?
No way!
Miyagawa said that he liked Karumi?
Seriously?
What the hell?
Miki's like Miyagawa for as long as I can remember!
Oh, she has been!
Learning Miyagawa her notebook and stuff like that!
She probably doesn't like it when any of the guys like a girl who isn't her!
She's just pretending to be interested!
That's awful!
Plus she called herself Karumi when her name's Ume!
I only let her into our group because I thought she'd make it easier for us to talk to the boys!
Hey guys!
If she ever has a real crush, we should ruin it for her!
She went out of her way to mess with us, so why not?!
Right?!
Hey, uh, you seem kinda... down lately...
No, I'm totally fine!
That's good!
See you tomorrow then!
Bye-bye!
Uh...
Practicing in the rain really sucks, though!
Wanna ditch?
You can't do that!
You're no fun!
Oh, hey!
You haven't gone home yet!
Something wrong?
Mm-mm...
It's nothing!
You sure?
Yeah!
You have practice, Kazehaya?
Mm-hmm!
I'm just grabbing something real quick!
Oh, I see!
Oh, I knew I left it here!
Good luck!
Thanks!
Uh...
Seriously...
You sure you're okay?
Whoa!
What is it?
He's so different.
He's popular and always surrounded by the other boys.
Same class again?
And yet...
He always sees me for who I am.
I won't tell anyone.
Not a single soul.
Nobody.
Not until...
The day Kazehaya falls for me.
Oh, hey, it's you.
I had no clue.
That said, you don't care even if Kazehaya finds out about this.
I can't believe it.
You actually have a crush on Pin!
I don't!
Oh!
I'm sorry.
That's rude of me, right?
You haven't heard?
About?
Uh...
What's her deal?
She pisses me off.
Acting like a saint.
Kazehaya?
Hm?
What kind of person is Sawako?
Hmm...
Kuro Numa's easily misunderstood.
But no matter how risky something might be, she always speaks the truth.
That's why, no matter what it is she tells me, I always believe her.
Risky?
Yeah.
She probably isn't aware of it, but...
If Kuro Numa were the type to always lay low and play it safe, I think it's possible even Yano and Yoshida wouldn't have fully believed her.
Even if we want to help her, she always ends up working things out herself.
That's just how she is.
She's really come a long way.
I understand.
So I'm sure he will, too, if you just talk to him.
What am I saying?
I sound so arrogant.
See ya.
Kazeh...
Cheer up, okay?
I didn't want Kazehaya to misunderstand.
I don't want him to misunderstand.
Please...
No...
Wait...
Kazehaya, wait!
You're wrong!
Pina isn't the person I like!
The one I really like is...
You, Kazehaya!
It was always you!
Only you!
Oh, Kazehaya...
Please stop thinking I like someone else!
I just can't...
I can't take it!
I'm so sorry about that.
Really.
I'm an idiot.
I'm sorry.
I know.
It's so obvious!
It's impossible...
For me to see anyone else but her.
So...
I'm sorry.
I know.
It's so obvious!
Kazehaya...
Kazehaya, does me telling you that I like you make you feel happy at all?
Yeah.
Thank you.
Just this once.
Call me by my name.
I know.
It's so obvious!
Kazehaya, does me telling you that I like you make you feel happy at all?
Oh?
Uh...
Yeah.
Thank you.
Just this once.
Call me by my name, okay?
My first name.
Ume.
Well, I suppose this granny name isn't as bad as I thought then.
Man, saying all this stuff wasn't my intention.
I really miscalculated.
Miscalculated?
The one who threw me off the most was...
Definitely you, Kazehaya.
Oh, you're making a huge mistake!
You'll never find a girl as cute as I am!
Also, how could you think I was into that idiot peen?
It's ridiculous!
There.
Much better.
That was...
Have you always been like this?
Kazehaya!
You have no eye for girls!
See ya!
Uh-oh.
I said it!
I can't help but wonder...
If we had liked different people...
Maybe we would've been able to understand each other better...
If only...
Huh?
Kazehaya?
Yes!
So I was right!
Oh, who'd've thought?
Wait, why are you playing dumb, Yanuchi?
And I thought it was embarrassing!
Uh, yeah, no reason.
Oh, really?
Hey, so did something happen that made you realize you liked him?
I guess...
It was...
What?
Talking about it all...
With Kurumi...
And if we didn't like the same person...
There are so many things I never would've realized...
With her, huh?
I had no idea that girls were capable of being so savage over a guy.
But I gotta hand it to her, cause that could never be me.
I-I don't know how I would be...
From all I know...
I could become a total monster!
Monster!
Monster?
Huh?
Who's this about?
But...
But anyway...
We're happy for you, Sawako.
Things are gonna get really interesting from here!
I said it...
I'm so glad...
I'm also glad...
That I was able to tell you, Kurumi...
And when you opened up and shared your feelings with me...
It meant...
So much more than you know...
Morning!
Oh, hey!
Huh?
Uh...
What's going on?
Why do you have those huge sunglasses?
It's none of your business!
Stop right there!
What's the deal with the shades?
In case you ever notice we're inside right now...
Hmm?
No!
You're that kid who's totally head over heels for me!
What?
Up crying after being rejected?
Well, I guess it can't be help, then.
Uh-huh. That's it.
Next time, make sure to fall for someone your own age.
High school boys are simple creatures.
It doesn't matter if he likes you or not.
If you confess your feelings to a guy,
He won't be able to stop thinking about you all day long, you know?
Uh-huh.
Boys are stupid like that!
See ya!
I wonder...
If that's true...
Alright!
I'm ready!
We're gonna win the rest of these soccer games!
I don't think anyone can beat you in spirit at the very least.
We'll win and enjoy that after party!
I better get serious too!
We totally lost!
Not that we ever had a chance, huh?
She looks...
Super stylish!
You look like you have business!
We'll go on ahead and wait, kay?
When I first recognized my feelings for Kaze Haya, I was happy too.
But I never joined in with the other girls ogling over him.
And I never told a single soul how much I liked him.
I just...
Kept it to myself.
But know this.
Even if you somehow manage to beat the million to one odds against you getting with Kaze Haya,
I will never, ever be able to say I'm happy for you.
Kay!
Cause if he likes a girl, I automatically hate her guts!
Does that mean we...
Can never be friends?
What do you mean friends?
I think you mean rivals.
So that's the word...
...Rifles.
Damn it!
This is just the worst!
Why the heck did I lose?
This really pisses me off!
Yeah.
It just isn't right.
We're mad too.
And we totally feel for you!
Hey, let's not make sure we're on the way home today.
So, uh...
What's the deal with her?
Who knows?
But you know what?
If she was like that from the beginning, I actually think I maybe wouldn't have hated her as much.
Seriously?
After that...
Our class ended up losing in every single event.
Yuck.
We watched Mr. Arai's soul leave his body.
And that was the end of our field day.
All right.
Guys, let's all head home and meet at six for the after party.
Yeah!
We ended up in six plays!
I'm proud.
We worked really hard.
Right?
My first...
After party...
I stopped by home...
And opened up my dictionary.
My very first...
Rival...
And so?
When did you first start liking him?
What about when you made that announcement?
Actually...
No, that would have been way before, wouldn't it?
I...
Think I already felt that way by then.
I do wonder though...
When I started to feel this way...
La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-
What song's good for you?
Oh, I'm gonna take a quick break.
I'll see next!
Seen Kuro Numa?
Yeah, she stepped out.
She was overheating, so she went outside to cool down.
Oh, thanks.
And I wonder who it is that made her start burning up.
Kuro Numa?
Hey!
She is out.
Sawako.
Sleep talking?
Really.
I was just thinking about it way too hard.
Sawako.
Sawako Kuro Numa, isn't it?
From that moment on,
my entire world
started to completely transform.
That's right.
Since the moment he called my name,
I'm certain
I'd already fallen in love.
dreamed of
vale
Nice!
Cool Bye!
Kuro Kuro home
영
What?
The
Thank you.
A nighttime get together. A simple exchange. Next time, night talk.
Next time, night talk.